Lunga Malinga

City of Johannesburg, Gauteng, South Africa



lungamalinga10@gmail.com



0783910030



linkedin.com/in/lunga-malinga-8775a9279

Summary

I'm a passionate software developer based in Soweto. My programming journey started back in 2014, Not knowing I'll fall in love, and ever since I never looked back. My work is focused on both back-end and front-end applications, and I enjoy doing both.

My expertise lies in developing high-quality software solutions across different domains. I am well-versed in JAVA, JavaScript, C#, PHP, Python, Microsoft SQL, Oracle PL/SQL, HTML, CSS, allowing me to adapt to different projects and contribute effectively to their success. I have a strong understanding of software development principles, algorithms, and data structures, which enables me to design efficient and optimised code.

I'm currently a software development student at WeThinkCode_, where I'm learning a lot of new things like Brownfields Development, Socket programming, and using tools like Git.

Experience



Salesforce Developer (Trainee)

Phynnel

Jul 2021 - Dec 2021 (6 months)

I was a Salesforce Developer Trainee for 5 months (from July 2021 to November 2021).

Intern (System Support)

Rennies BCD Travel

Jun 2017 - May 2018 (1 year)

Education



WeThinkCode

Software Development

Sep 2022 - Dec 2023



IIE Rosebank College

Higher National Diploma, Software Development Jan 2014 - Dec 2016

Skills

macOS • Brownfields Development • Socket Programming • Microsoft Excel • Microsoft Word • Microsoft Outlook • Gitlab • Git • C# • Microsoft SQL Server